{
    "id": "c239f9bdbf0449f29e90c64b6f448e62",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is the church .............................. was built in the 16th century.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a44266884b84423d927dbbbcb4bcff36"
        },
        {
            "question": "John .................................. is very industrious was rewarded.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0e3ef6d135924e5c9a074e0a66880e02"
        },
        {
            "question": "The parcel ..................................... was sent by my mother reached me this morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4160823e44324724a7853c6f49622fe8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mark ........................................ is always late for work was reprimanded by his boss.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "89af9e49f35d440098c5e042285b041c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met my uncle ........................................ had just returned from the US.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3af60475e2a74c64aa1e270c59c71f10"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ........................................ my grandfather built.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f044bcb9e1d04365814cd190f6826dec"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girls ............................................ I was speaking of have arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc378dc78a414a57a4c5d837bc07c3c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know a man ......................................... wears a prosthetic leg.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "whom",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2f11419efe2543bf9397b3a2175ff7fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard some news ..................................... disturbed me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6b3baae3411347d1912e656b287dbbf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the cat .......................................... killed the rat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6a28060374314e6d9ab2c91ff4e9282a"
        }
    ]
}